vicesisters.com 2009-06-17

# Privacy Policy - Free escort listing, ViceSisters

Privacy Policy

**1\. A Special Note About Children** Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We ask that children not submit information to us. 

**2\. About ViceSisters**  
ViceSisters is an online network which provides you useful tools to find consenting adult relationships online. ViceSisters service is FREE to all people browsing and to all who would like to create an account and be listed on our search engine. 

**3\. Information We Collect**  
In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites collect this sort of information. We may tie your IP address to your personally identifiable information. We will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. I We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in your profiles. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Use. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies. A session ID cookie simply terminates once a user closes the browser. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

**3\. Our Use of Your Information**  
We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to comply with applicable law, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs. We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. 

**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. Information such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed.  
In order to maintain a healthy community, ViceSisters cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

**5\. Your use of Other Users' Information**  
You may not use other user's information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. ViceSisters reserves the right to terminate those who misuse other user's information or who otherwise violate the ViceSisters Terms of Use. 

**6\. Control of Your Password**  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

**7\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personally identifiable information at ViceSisters including:  
Your email address  
Your city, state, zip code, country  
Your password  
Your profile  
Please promptly update your information if it changes by logging in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information. 

**8\. Third Party Collections of Information**  
Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. While ViceSisters is working closely with our partners to ensure the highest privacy to you, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

**9\. Security**  
ViceSisters has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.ViceSisters uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at ViceSisters work hard to ensure your secure use of our services. 

**10\. Update/Delete**  
ViceSisters Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database:  
Send an email to Customer Service;  
Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile;  
Call us at (718) 407-4217  

**11\. TRUSTe Privacy Program**  
ViceSisters is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that ViceSisters is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
support@vicesisters.com 

**12\. Payment and Credit Card Information Privacy**  
ViceSisters hereby certify that under no circumstances will any credit card number be stored in the system after completing the transaction, whether successfully or not, except 4 last digits for security and verification purposes only. ViceSisters also certifies, that no personal , accounting or any other user information will be transferred to the third-party organizations, unless such action is required by and complies to section 4 of ViceSisters Privacy Policy.
